A Guide to the Institute of International Education records, Alumni and Historical Files, RG 1 FA1289
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Historical Files, 3
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship Servel, Inc. N.Y. - 1942-47 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 5), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 5 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship Shell Chemical Co. San Francisco - 1947 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 6), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 6 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship Singmaster and Breyer, N.Y. - 1948 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 7), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 7 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship Skinner Engine Co. Eire, Penna. - 1948 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 8), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 8 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship Smith, Hinchman and Grylls, Inc. Detroit, Michigan - 1943-47 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 9), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 9 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship Spaulding-Rex-Deswarte Los Angeles, CA - 1948 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 10), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 10 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship Standard Oil Co. of N.J., N.Y. - 1945-48 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 11), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 11 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship Stark Bros. Nurseries and Orchard Co. Louisiana, Missouri - 1942-46 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 12), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 12 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship Dept. of State Correspondence - 1946-47 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 13), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 13 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship Edward Stern and Co., Inc. Philadelphia - 1946-47 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 14), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 14 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship St. Joseph Lead Co. N.Y. 1943-46 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 15), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 15 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship Chinese Naval Training Program War Clearences 1945-47 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 16), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 16 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship United States Life Insurance Co. N.Y. - 1946-47 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 17), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 17 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship U.S. Steel Export Co. N.Y. - 1944-47 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 18), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 18 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship United States Sugar Corp. Clewiston, Fla. - 1944-47 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 19), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 19 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship Stromberg-Carlson Tel. Mfg. Co. Rochester, N.Y. - 1944-47 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 20), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 20 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship Sun Shipbuilding and Drydock Co. Chester, PA. - 1942-46 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 21), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 21 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship Western Electric Co., Inc. Washington, D.C. - 1943-47 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 22), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 22 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship Westinghouse Air Brake Co. Wilmerding, PA. - 1942-47 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 23), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 23 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship Westinghouse Electric Intl. N.Y. - 1945-48 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 24), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 24 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship West Virginia State Road Commission - 1944-47 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 25), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 25 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship Weyerhaeuser Timber Co. Tacoma, Washington - 1942-47 (Reel 22, Side 2, Index 26), Reel 22, Side 2, Index 26 (Reel 22)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship The White Motor Co. Cleveland - 1942-47 (Reel 23, Side 1, Index 1), Reel 23, Side 1, Index 1 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship Worthington Pump And Machinery Corp. Harrison, N.J. - 1946-47 (Reel 23, Side 1, Index 2), Reel 23, Side 1, Index 2 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - IIE Washington Conference Report Finances and Reports - 1947-48 (Reel 23, Side 1, Index 5), Reel 23, Side 1, Index 5 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Daily File-Eloise De La O - 1948 (Reel 23, Side 1, Index 6), Reel 23, Side 1, Index 6 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects General - Parker and Company Insurance Claims reimbursed - 1948 (Reel 17, Side 1, Index 1), Reel 17, Side 1, Index 1 (Reel 17)
  - Trainees - Special Projects General - Parker and Company Insurance Claims reimbursed - 1949 (Reel 17, Side 1, Index 2), Reel 17, Side 1, Index 2 (Reel 17)
  - Trainees - Special Projects - Inter-American Trade Scholarship Jorge Angel Vallejo-Colombia - 1944-48 (Reel 23, Side 1, Index 8), Reel 23, Side 1, Index 8 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects - Inter-American Trade Scholarship Ramon Enrique Alvarez-Panama - 1946-47 (Reel 23, Side 1, Index 9), Reel 23, Side 1, Index 9 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees Inter-American Trade Scholarship Pedro Arias-Ecuador - 1944-47 (Reel 23, Side 1, Index 10), Reel 23, Side 1, Index 10 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Oscar Balladares - Nicaragua Unsuccesful - 1946-47 (Reel 23, Side 1, Index 7), Reel 23, Side 1, Index 7 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects - Inter-American Trade Scholarship Guzman Antonio Barreiro-Uruguay - 1945-46 (Reel 23, Side 1, Index 11), Reel 23, Side 1, Index 11 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects - Inter-American Trade Scholarship Guzman Antonio Barreiro-Uruguay - 1946-47 (Reel 23, Side 1, Index 12), Reel 23, Side 1, Index 12 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects - Inter-American Trade Scholarship Jaime De Jesus Botero-Colombia - 1944-47 (Reel 23, Side 1, Index 13), Reel 23, Side 1, Index 13 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects - Inter-American Trade Scholarship Wilson Carlos De Andrade-Brazil - 1945-48 (Reel 23, Side 1, Index 14), Reel 23, Side 1, Index 14 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects - Inter-American Trade Scholarship Jesus Ivan Arango-Colombia - 1946-48 (Reel 23, Side 1, Index 15), Reel 23, Side 1, Index 15 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects - Inter-American Trade Scholarship Miguel Enique Arregui-Euador Unsuccessful - 1946 (Reel 23, Side 1, Index 16), Reel 23, Side 1, Index 16 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects - Inter-American Trade Scholarship Jesus Ivan Arango-Colombia - 1944-45 (Reel 23, Side 1, Index 17), Reel 23, Side 1, Index 17 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects - Inter-American Trade Scholarship Abel Pindaro Brandao-Panama (Panama-U.S. Training program) - 1946-47 (Reel 23, Side 1, Index 18), Reel 23, Side 1, Index 18 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects - Inter-American Trade Scholarship Aurelio Brandao-Panama (Panama-U.S. Training Program) - 1946-47 (Reel 23, Side 1, Index 19), Reel 23, Side 1, Index 19 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects - Inter-American Trade Scholarship Carlos Dios Brosch-Brazil - 1945-48 (Reel 23, Side 2, Index 1), Reel 23, Side 2, Index 1 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Carlos Brosch-Brazil Photostats of Douments - Application - 1945 (Reel 23, Side 2, Index 2), Reel 23, Side 2, Index 2 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Domingo Alberto Cadiz-Chile - 1946-47 (Reel 23, Side 2, Index 3), Reel 23, Side 2, Index 3 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Juan Campbell-Argentina - 1945-48 (Reel 23, Side 2, Index 4), Reel 23, Side 2, Index 4 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Guillermo Leonardo Castillo-Ecuador - 1947-48 (Reel 23, Side 2, Index 5), Reel 23, Side 2, Index 5 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Mario F. Castro-Bolivia - 1944-48 (Reel 23, Side 2, Index 6), Reel 23, Side 2, Index 6 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Lucien Decatrel-Haiti - 1945-47 (Reel 23, Side 2, Index 7), Reel 23, Side 2, Index 7 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Guillermo D'Orey Panama (Panama-U.S. Training Program) - 1946 (Reel 23, Side 2, Index 8), Reel 23, Side 2, Index 8 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Manuel Edgardo Duron-Honduras - 1947 (Reel 23, Side 2, Index 9), Reel 23, Side 2, Index 9 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Manuel Maria Estrada-Venezuela - 1945-47 (Reel 23, Side 2, Index 10), Reel 23, Side 2, Index 10 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Manuel Maria Estrada-Venezuela Application File (Photostats) (Reel 23, Side 2, Index 11), Reel 23, Side 2, Index 11 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Fernando Enrique Flores-Panama (Panama-U.S. Training Program) - 1946-48 (Reel 23, Side 2, Index 12), Reel 23, Side 2, Index 12 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Heny Forno-Guatemala - 1947 (Reel 23, Side 2, Index 13), Reel 23, Side 2, Index 13 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Humberto Garci-Aguirre--Guatemala - 1947 (Reel 23, Side 2, Index 14), Reel 23, Side 2, Index 14 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Oscar Armando Garcia-Honduras - 1947 (Reel 23, Side 2, Index 15), Reel 23, Side 2, Index 15 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Francisco Hector Goni-Uruguay - 1945-47 (Reel 23, Side 2, Index 16), Reel 23, Side 2, Index 16 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Luis Alberto Gonzalez-Ecuador - 1947-48 (Reel 23, Side 2, Index 17), Reel 23, Side 2, Index 17 (Reel 23)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Eduardo Gonzalez-Ecuador - 1947 (Reel 24, Side 1, Index 1), Reel 24, Side 1, Index 1 (Reel 24)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Luis Alberto Gonzalez-Ecuador - 1945-47 (Reel 24, Side 1, Index 2), Reel 24, Side 1, Index 2 (Reel 24)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Nester Gonzalez-Colombia - 1945-47 (Reel 24, Side 1, Index 3), Reel 24, Side 1, Index 3 (Reel 24)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Gustavo Goyzueta-Peru - 1946-50 (Reel 24, Side 1, Index 4), Reel 24, Side 1, Index 4 (Reel 24)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Juan Antonio Gutierrez-Panama (Panama-U.S. Training Program) - 1946 (Reel 24, Side 1, Index 5), Reel 24, Side 1, Index 5 (Reel 24)
  - Trainees - Special Projects Inter-American Trade Scholarship Fritz F. Johansen Jr.-Brazil - 1946-47 (Reel 24, Side 1, Index 6), Reel 24, Side 1, Index 6 (Reel 24)
  - Iraq - 1944 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 25), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 25 (Reel 13)
  - Iraq - 1946 (Reel 14, Side 2, Index 27), Reel 14, Side 2, Index 27 (Reel 14)
  - Iraq General - 1948-50 (Reel 20, Side 1, Index 13), Reel 20, Side 1, Index 13 (Reel 20)
  - Israel - Selection Committee U.S. Embassy - Tel-Aviv General Correspondence - 1948-49 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 26), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 26 (Reel 29)
  - Israel - Selection Committee U.S. Embassy - Tel-Aviv Correspondence - 1950-51 - 1950 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 27), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 27 (Reel 29)
  - Israel - Seagram Fellowship Re Establishing Program - 1950 (Reel 19, Side 2, Index 26), Reel 19, Side 2, Index 26 (Reel 19)
  - Israel - Selection Committee U.S. Embassy - Tel-Aviv Correspondence - 1951-52 - 1951 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 28), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 28 (Reel 29)
  - Israel - Selection Committee U.S. Embassy - Tel-Aviv General Correspondence - 1952 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 29), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 29 (Reel 29)
  - Israel - Student Exchange General Correspondence - 1953-54 American Embassy - Tel-Aviv - 1953 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 30), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 30 (Reel 29)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board - 1919 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 15), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 15 (Reel 2)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board and Meetings - 1920 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 17), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 17 (Reel 2)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board - 1921 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 20), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 20 (Reel 2)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board - 1927 (Reel 18, Side 1, Index 7), Reel 18, Side 1, Index 7 (Reel 18)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board - 1928 (Reel 18, Side 1, Index 8), Reel 18, Side 1, Index 8 (Reel 18)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board - 1931 (Reel 2, Side 2, Index 24), Reel 2, Side 2, Index 24 (Reel 2)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board - 1932 (Reel 18, Side 1, Index 17), Reel 18, Side 1, Index 17 (Reel 18)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board - 1934 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 14), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 14 (Reel 10)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board - 1935 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 16), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 16 (Reel 10)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board - 1936 (Reel 4, Side 2, Index 27), Reel 4, Side 2, Index 27 (Reel 4)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board - 1937 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 23), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 23 (Reel 7)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board - 1938 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 49), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 49 (Reel 7)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board - 1939 (Reel 10, Side 1, Index 4), Reel 10, Side 1, Index 4 (Reel 10)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board - 1940 (Reel 10, Side 8, Index 8), Reel 10, Side 8, Index 8 (Reel 10)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board - 1940, 1942, 1945-46 (Reel 18, Side 1, Index 22), Reel 18, Side 1, Index 22 (Reel 18)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board - 1942 (Reel 12, Side 1, Index 14), Reel 12, Side 1, Index 14 (Reel 12)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board - 1944 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 55), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 55 (Reel 13)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board - 1944 (Reel 13, Side 2, Index 14), Reel 13, Side 2, Index 14 (Reel 13)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board Mid-West Trip Report - 1945 (Reel 14, Side 1, Index 19), Reel 14, Side 1, Index 19 (Reel 14)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board - 1946 (Reel 14, Side 2, Index 6), Reel 14, Side 2, Index 6 (Reel 14)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board - 1946 (Reel 14, Side 2, Index 7), Reel 14, Side 2, Index 7 (Reel 14)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board Resolution on Retirement of Dr. Duggan - 1946 (Reel 17, Side 2, Index 19), Reel 17, Side 2, Index 19 (Reel 17)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board Executive Committee Mrs. Samuel A. Lewison - 1947-50 (Reel 17, Side 2, Index 22), Reel 17, Side 2, Index 22 (Reel 17)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board Letter Re Recruiting New Trustees - 1948 (Reel 17, Side 2, Index 20), Reel 17, Side 2, Index 20 (Reel 17)
  - I.I.E. Suggestions for Developing the Institute - 1919 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 12), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 12 (Reel 2)
  - I.I.E. Advisory Council - 1919 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 16), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 16 (Reel 2)
  - I.I.E. Early Organization - 1917-20, 1923-24 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 13), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 13 (Reel 2)
  - I.I.E. Carnegie Endowment Grants - 1920-23 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 24), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 24 (Reel 2)
  - I.I.E. Reorganization - 1924-26 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 26), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 26 (Reel 2)
  - I.I.E. Housing the Institute - 1919-25 - Dr. Duggan's Trip 1919 Publicity - 1920-21 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 14), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 14 (Reel 2)
  - I.I.E. Administrative Board Meetings - Minutes - 1922-23 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 23), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 23 (Reel 2)
  - I.I.E. Reorganization and Administrative Board - 1924-25 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 27), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 27 (Reel 2)
  - I.I.E. Field Trip Reports (Alphabetical order by Institutions) - 1951 (Reel 19, Side 2, Index 20), Reel 19, Side 2, Index 20 (Reel 19)
  - I.I.E. Bureau Divisions Correspondence - Letters from Ambassadors - 1920-25 (Reel 2, Side 1, Index 19), Reel 2, Side 1, Index 19 (Reel 2)
  - I.I.E. Franco-American Exchange - 1919-25 (Reel 2, Side 2, Index 7), Reel 2, Side 2, Index 7 (Reel 2)
  - I.I.E. Survey of American and Foreign Ex-Fellows - 1929 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 9), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 9 (Reel 3)
  - I.I.E. Organization - 1931 (Reel 2, Side 2, Index 19), Reel 2, Side 2, Index 19 (Reel 2)
  - IIE Report on Status of IIE (Letter) - 1931 (Reel 17, Side 2, Index 10), Reel 17, Side 2, Index 10 (Reel 17)
  - IIE Edward R. Murrow European Trip - 1932 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 8), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 8 (Reel 10)
  - IIE Report of Edward R. Murrow from London on European Trip - 1932 (Reel 17, Side 2, Index 11), Reel 17, Side 2, Index 11 (Reel 17)
  - IIE Organization - General Correspondence - 1933 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 14), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 14 (Reel 18)
  - IIE General - 1934 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 8), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 8 (Reel 11)
  - IIE General A-Z - 1934 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 9), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 9 (Reel 11)
  - IIE Organization - General - 1934 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 15), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 15 (Reel 10)
  - IIE Camp - General - 1934 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 10), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 10 (Reel 11)
  - IIE Organization - General - 1935 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 21), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 21 (Reel 10)
  - IIE Re 15th Annual Report - 1935 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 25), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 25 (Reel 10)
  - IIE Re Articles Published - 1935 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 26), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 26 (Reel 10)
  - IIE Re Bulletins - 1935 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 27), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 27 (Reel 10)
  - IIE News Bulletin General - 1935 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 20), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 20 (Reel 10)
  - IIE Bureau Divisions - 1936 (Reel 5, Side 1, Index 17), Reel 5, Side 1, Index 17 (Reel 5)
  - IIE Spanish Bureau 1936 Istituto De Las Espanas (Reel 5, Side 1, Index 19), Reel 5, Side 1, Index 19 (Reel 5)
  - IIE Organization - General - 1936-37 (Reel 5, Side 1, Index 16), Reel 5, Side 1, Index 16 (Reel 5)
  - IIE Bureau Divisions - 1937 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 24), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 24 (Reel 7)
  - IIE Organization - General - 1938 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 17), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 17 (Reel 7)
  - IIE Annual Report - 1938 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 38), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 38 (Reel 7)
  - IIE Annual Report - 1938 (Letter) (Reel 8, Side 1, Index 4), Reel 8, Side 1, Index 4 (Reel 8)
  - IIE Correspondence Re 20th Annual Report - 1940 (Reel 10, Side 1, Index 34), Reel 10, Side 1, Index 34 (Reel 10)
  - IIE Correspondence Re 21st Annual Report - 1940 (Reel 10, Side 1, Index 32), Reel 10, Side 1, Index 32 (Reel 10)
  - IIE Spanish Bureau - Istituto De Las Espanas - 1940 (Reel 10, Side 1, Index 35), Reel 10, Side 1, Index 35 (Reel 10)
  - IIE Misc. Budget and Administration - 1935-37, 1941-42, 1946-48 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 22), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 22 (Reel 18)
  - IIE General Administration and Budget - 1943-47 (Reel 18, Side 2, Index 23), Reel 18, Side 2, Index 23 (Reel 18)
  - Re 22nd Annual Report - 1942 (Reel 12, Side 1, Index 15), Reel 12, Side 1, Index 15 (Reel 12)
  - IIE Spanish Bureau - 1942 (Reel 12, Side 1, Index 18), Reel 12, Side 1, Index 18 (Reel 12)
  - IIE Annual Report - 1943 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 48), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 48 (Reel 13)
  - IIE Re 25th Annual Report - 1944 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 47), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 47 (Reel 13)
  - IIE General Washington Bureau - 1944 (Reel 14, Side 1, Index 1), Reel 14, Side 1, Index 1 (Reel 14)
  - IIE General Washington Bureau - 1944 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 22), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 22 (Reel 13)
  - IIE 25th Anniversary Dinner General - 1945 (Reel 14, Side 1, Index 26), Reel 14, Side 1, Index 26 (Reel 14)
  - IIE General Correspondence Re Selection of Successor to Dr. Stephen Duggan - 1946 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 7), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 7 (Reel 15)
  - IIE General Washington Bureau - 1946 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 1), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 1 (Reel 15)
  - IIE Correspondence Re Finances - 1946 (Reel 15, Side 1, Index 6), Reel 15, Side 1, Index 6 (Reel 15)
  - IIE - Washington Bureau Quarterly Reports - 1947 (Reel 29, Side 1, Index 5), Reel 29, Side 1, Index 5 (Reel 29)
  - IIE Washington Office Periodic Reports - George Hall - 1947-49 (Reel 17, Side 1, Index 5), Reel 17, Side 1, Index 5 (Reel 17)
  - IIE Re 19th Annual Report - 1948 (Reel 15, Side 2, Index 1), Reel 15, Side 2, Index 1 (Reel 15)
  - IIE Advisory Committee on Graduate Studies - Minutes - 1948-1950 (Reel 17, Side 1, Index 33), Reel 17, Side 1, Index 33 (Reel 17)
  - IIE Public Relations Department of State - Austria - 1949 (Reel 17, Side 1, Index 6), Reel 17, Side 1, Index 6 (Reel 17)
  - IIE Presidency Candidates A-G - 1949 (Reel 16, Side 2, Index 13), Reel 16, Side 2, Index 13 (Reel 16)
  - IIE Presidency Candidates H-L - 1949 (Reel 16, Side 2, Index 14), Reel 16, Side 2, Index 14 (Reel 16)
  - IIE Presidency Re Selection of Successor to Laurence Duggan M-Z - 1949 (Reel 16, Side 2, Index 15), Reel 16, Side 2, Index 15 (Reel 16)
  - IIE Presidency Re Selection of Successor to Laurence Duggan - 1949 (Reel 16, Side 2, Index 16), Reel 16, Side 2, Index 16 (Reel 16)
  - IIE Paris Office - 1948-49 (Report of Professor Atkinson - 1945) (Reel 17, Side 2, Index 4), Reel 17, Side 2, Index 4 (Reel 17)
  - IIE Paris Office Dr. Albert George - 1949-51 (Reel 17, Side 2, Index 3), Reel 17, Side 2, Index 3 (Reel 17)
  - IIE European Office - Paris Correspondence Re French Matters - 1949 (Reel 17, Side 1, Index 8), Reel 17, Side 1, Index 8 (Reel 17)
  - IIE Paris Office - 1949 (Reel 17, Side 1, Index 4), Reel 17, Side 1, Index 4 (Reel 17)
  - IIE Paris Office - 1950 (Reel 17, Side 2, Index 2), Reel 17, Side 2, Index 2 (Reel 17)
  - IIE Washington Office - 1950 (Reel 19, Side 2, Index 13), Reel 19, Side 2, Index 13 (Reel 19)
  - General - IIE Re 29th Annual Report - 1950 (Reel 19, Side 2, Index 6), Reel 19, Side 2, Index 6 (Reel 19)
  - IIE Development and Information Program - Bess M. Trinks General Correspondence - 1950 (Reel 17, Side 2, Index 21), Reel 17, Side 2, Index 21 (Reel 17)
  - Ireland - 1944 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 18), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 18 (Reel 13)
  - Ireland Irish Exchange - 1946 (Reel 14, Side 2, Index 25), Reel 14, Side 2, Index 25 (Reel 14)
  - Ireland - Student Exchange Annual Letters, etc. - 1950-53 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 23), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 23 (Reel 29)
  - Ireland Selection Committee Correspondence - 1953-54 - 1953 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 25), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 25 (Reel 29)
  - Ireland Department of State Correspondence - 1953-54, 1952, 1953 (Reel 29, Side 2, Index 24), Reel 29, Side 2, Index 24 (Reel 29)
  - Ireland Selection Committee (Department of State Quoto List) - 1957-58 (Reel 30, Side 1, Index 35), Reel 30, Side 1, Index 35 (Reel 30)
  - Ireland Department of State (IES) Correspondence - 1957-58 - 1957 (Reel 30, Side 1, Index 36), Reel 30, Side 1, Index 36 (Reel 30)
  - Italy America Society Italian Professorship (Reel 2, Side 2, Index 5), Reel 2, Side 2, Index 5 (Reel 2)
  - Italy International Centre In Florence (Villa Collina Ridente) 1930 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 8), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 8 (Reel 3)
  - Special Projects Italy 1931 (Reel 8, Side 1, Index 8), Reel 8, Side 1, Index 8 (Reel 8)
  - Special Projects Italy 1932 (Reel 8, Side 1, Index 23), Reel 8, Side 1, Index 23 (Reel 8)
  - Special Projects Italy 1932 Dr. Averardi, Professor Borgese (Reel 8, Side 1, Index 22), Reel 8, Side 1, Index 22 (Reel 8)
  - Italy 1933 (Reel 4, Side 1, Index 31), Reel 4, Side 1, Index 31 (Reel 4)
  - Italy 1933 (Reel 4, Side 2, Index 6), Reel 4, Side 2, Index 6 (Reel 4)
  - Italy Washington 1933 (Reel 4, Side 2, Index 7), Reel 4, Side 2, Index 7 (Reel 4)
  - Italy America Society 1933 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 5), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 5 (Reel 11)
  - Italy Assistantships to Italy Extracts of Reports 1933-1940 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 17), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 17 (Reel 6)
  - Italy 1934 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 28), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 28 (Reel 11)
  - Italy Secondary Schools 1934 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 29), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 29 (Reel 11)
  - Italy Washington, Dr. Parini and Dr. De Peverelli (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 30), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 30 (Reel 11)